{
    "subject": "resource/Gary_Larson",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tacoma,_Washington",
    "human_readable": "Gary Larson was born in Tacoma, Washington.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8892767429351807,
            "question": "Where was Gary Larson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8668968677520752,
            "question": "In what state was Gary Larson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8494059443473816,
            "question": "Name the city of Gary Larson's birth."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783165454864502,
            "question": "Was Gary Larson born in a city or rural area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7675349712371826,
            "question": "What year was Gary Larson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6700540781021118,
            "question": "Where did Gary Larson grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.508397102355957,
            "question": "What is Gary Larson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19753152132034302,
            "question": "What type of work did Gary Larson create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19501715898513794,
            "question": "Is Tacoma, Washington a large or small city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13930605351924896,
            "question": "What is the name of the comic strip created by Gary Larson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gary Larson was born in Tacoma, Washington.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8043_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tacoma, Washington a large or small city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8043_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Gary Larson create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8043_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Gary Larson known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8043_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8043_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently provide information that Gary Larson was born in Tacoma, Washington."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}